{
  "trivia": [
    {
      "topic": "General",
      "questions": [
        {
          "difficulty": "Easy",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "",
              "answer": ""
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the highest cost for a unit in the game currently?",
              "answer": "60"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much energy do Wizard quests cost?",
              "answer": "30"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much energy do Ultimate quests cost?",
              "answer": "40"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who is the developer of Crash Fever?",
              "answer": "Wonderplanet"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the premium currency in-game?",
              "answer": "Polygon"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the **non**-premium currency in-game?",
              "answer": "Bits"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many Normal Quest are there?",
              "answer": "31"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much energy do Easy quests cost?",
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much energy do Normal quests cost?",
              "answer": "15"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much energy do Hard quests cost?",
              "answer": "20"
            },
            {
              "question": "What color beats Red?",
              "answer": "Blue"
            },
            {
              "question": "What color beats Blue?",
              "answer": "Yellow"
            },
            {
              "question": "What color beats Yellow?",
              "answer": "Green"
            },
            {
              "question": "What color beats Green?",
              "answer": "Red"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create a CP without buffs?",
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create a SCP without buffs?",
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the maximum length chain possible?",
              "answer": "46"
            },
            {
              "question": "**High** CP boost makes it easier to make a CP by how many panels?",
              "answer": "2"
            },
            {
              "question": "**Massive** CP boost makes it easier to make a CP by how many panels?",
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "**Ultra** CP boost makes it easier to make a CP by how many panels?",
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "**Immense** CP boost makes it easier to make a CP by how many panels?",
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create CP with **high** CP boost?",
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create CP with **massive** CP boost?",
              "answer": "2"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create CP with **ultra** CP boost?",
              "answer": "1"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create SCP with **high** CP boost?",
              "answer": "10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create SCP with **massive** CP boost?",
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create SCP with **ultra** CP boost?",
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the minimum chain size to create SCP with **immense** CP boost?",
              "answer": "1"
            },
            {
              "question": "What does CP stand for?",
              "answer": "Crash Panel"
            },
            {
              "question": "What does SCP stand for?",
              "answer": "Super Crash Panel"
            },
            {
              "question": "What does CBP stand for?",
              "answer": "Color break panel"
            },
            {
              "question": "What do you usually feed units for EXP?",
              "answer": "Ducks"
            },
            {
              "question": "What currency do you use to pull on the enhancement hatcher?",
              "answer": "Links"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much polygon does it cost to do a single pull on a hatcher?",
              "answer": "50"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much polygon does it usually cost to do a 10x pull on a hatcher?",
              "answer": "500"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much polygon does it cost to do a 10x pull on a hatcher if it is discounted?",
              "answer": "250"
            },
            {
              "question": "What panel explodes and converts the area around it?",
              "answer": "Paint"
            },
            {
              "question": "What gimmick are you normally unable to break?",
              "answer": "Junk"
            },
            {
              "question": "What gimmick damages you when you take it?",
              "answer": "Damage"
            },
            {
              "question": "What gimmick do you have to clear twice? ",
              "answer": "Protect"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much REC does a unit get when at +99 blue apples?",
              "answer": "693"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much ATK does a unit get when at +99 red apples?",
              "answer": "990"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much HP does a unit get when at +99 green apples?",
              "answer": "1485"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many bugs does a max bug 6* unit have?",
              "answer": "99"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many bugs does a max bug 5* unit have?",
              "answer": "75"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many times a day do duck hunt quests appear?",
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the world of Crash Fever called?",
              "answer": "Alice"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP does a Global Ducksworth give to a unit of the same color?",
              "answer": "1500000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP does a Global Ducksworth give to a unit of a different color?",
              "answer": "1000000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much ATK does an attack fruit give?",
              "answer": "10"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much ATK does a Mega attack fruit give?",
              "answer": "30"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much ATK does a Giga attack fruit give?",
              "answer": "100"
            },
            {
              "question": "What are some units in Crash Fever infected by?",
              "answer": "C virus"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much ATK does a Tera attack fruit give?",
              "answer": "200"
            },
            {
              "question": "What panel deals damage to you after a certain amount of turns if not destroyed?",
              "answer": "Timer"
            },
            {
              "question": "What cost are units that come from Ultimate stages?",
              "answer": "50"
            },
            {
              "question": "What cost are units that come from Wizard stages?",
              "answer": "45"
            },
            {
              "question": "What cost are Festival units?",
              "answer": "55"
            },
            {
              "question": "What chat command is often used to signify 'skip turn'?",
              "answer": "Defend"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Strength cost?",
              "answer": "200000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Lovers cost?",
              "answer": "200000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Chariot cost?",
              "answer": "200000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Nessebar cost?",
              "answer": "65000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Lemuria cost?",
              "answer": "65000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Megallanica cost?",
              "answer": "65000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Magician cost?",
              "answer": "200000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many ghosts does Troy/Trojan cost?",
              "answer": "65000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many FES/Rank ticket pieces does it take to form an entire ticket?",
              "answer": "5"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many rank points does it cost to purchase a rank unit?",
              "answer": "10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Easy** Awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Cat"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Normal** Awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Hare"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Hard** Awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Caterpillar"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Blue Legend** awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Turtle"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Red Legend** awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Dodo"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Yellow Legend** awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Dormouse"
            },
            {
              "question": "What type of animal is obtained from **Green Legend** awakening quests?",
              "answer": "Griffon"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who is the boss of Tower of the Queen: Chandille?",
              "answer": "Sophia"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who is the boss of Tower of the Queen: Elfram?",
              "answer": "Rose"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who is the boss of Tower of the Queen: Avaricia?",
              "answer": "Bonanza"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many days is the Daily Login reward rotation?",
              "answer": "8"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "difficulty": "Medium",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "What is the cost increase when awakening from 5* to 6*?",
              "answer": "15"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the cost increase when awakening from 4* to 5*?",
              "answer": "10"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP is gained for a Wizard quest?",
              "answer": "4500"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP is gained for an Ultimate quest?",
              "answer": "5200"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP is gained for a Ranked quest?",
              "answer": "4200"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **1st** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Entering the Mainframe"
            },
            {
              "question": "At what chain length is the CP damage at 100%?",
              "answer": "11"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the damage amplifier of a **High** damage single-target CP?",
              "answer": "2"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the damage amplifier of a **Massive** damage single-target CP?",
              "answer": "2.25"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the damage amplifier of an **Ultra** damage single-target CP?",
              "answer": "2.5"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the damage amplifier of an **Immense** damage single-target CP?",
              "answer": "2.75"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 46 chain CP?",
              "answer": "450"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 6 chain CP?",
              "answer": "50"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 7 chain CP?",
              "answer": "60"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of an 8 chain CP?",
              "answer": "70"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 9 chain CP?",
              "answer": "80"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 10 chain CP?",
              "answer": "90"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 11 chain CP?",
              "answer": "100"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 12 chain CP?",
              "answer": "110"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 13 chain CP?",
              "answer": "120"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 14 chain CP?",
              "answer": "130"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 15 chain CP?",
              "answer": "140"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 16 chain CP?",
              "answer": "150"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 17 chain CP?",
              "answer": "160"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 18 chain CP?",
              "answer": "170"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 19 chain CP?",
              "answer": "180"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 20 chain CP?",
              "answer": "190"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 21 chain CP?",
              "answer": "200"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 22 chain CP?",
              "answer": "210"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 23 chain CP?",
              "answer": "220"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 24 chain CP?",
              "answer": "230"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 25 chain CP?",
              "answer": "240"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 26 chain CP?",
              "answer": "250"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 27 chain CP?",
              "answer": "260"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 28 chain CP?",
              "answer": "270"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 29 chain CP?",
              "answer": "280"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 30 chain CP?",
              "answer": "290"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 31 chain CP?",
              "answer": "300"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 32 chain CP?",
              "answer": "310"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 33 chain CP?",
              "answer": "320"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 34 chain CP?",
              "answer": "330"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 35 chain CP?",
              "answer": "340"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 36 chain CP?",
              "answer": "350"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 37 chain CP?",
              "answer": "360"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 38 chain CP?",
              "answer": "370"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 39 chain CP?",
              "answer": "380"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 40 chain CP?",
              "answer": "390"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 41 chain CP?",
              "answer": "400"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 42 chain CP?",
              "answer": "410"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 43 chain CP?",
              "answer": "420"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 44 chain CP?",
              "answer": "430"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the power in % of a 45 chain CP?",
              "answer": "440"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the bit cost per unit used to enhance a **level 1** unit?",
              "answer": "100"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the bit cost per unit used to enhance a **level 99** unit?",
              "answer": "990"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much HP does a vitality fruit give?",
              "answer": "15"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much HP does a Mega vitality fruit give?",
              "answer": "45"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much HP does a Giga vitality fruit give?",
              "answer": "150"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much HP does a Tera vitality fruit give?",
              "answer": "300"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many servers are there?",
              "answer": "5"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Longinus come from?",
              "answer": "Spear"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Excalibur come from?",
              "answer": "Sword"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Gambanteinn come from?",
              "answer": "Staff"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Gae Bolg come from?",
              "answer": "Spear"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Trident come from?",
              "answer": "Spear"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Gungnir come from?",
              "answer": "Spear"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Ame no Murakumo come from?",
              "answer": "Blade"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Muramasa come from?",
              "answer": "Blade"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Masamune come from?",
              "answer": "Blade"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Laevateinn come from?",
              "answer": "Sword"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Balmung come from?",
              "answer": "Sword"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Onimaru Kunitsuna come from?",
              "answer": "Blade"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Lindsay come from?",
              "answer": "Christmas"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Poinsettia come from?",
              "answer": "Christmas"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Velvet come from?",
              "answer": "Christmas"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Graham come from?",
              "answer": "Sword"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do Nurupon cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "25000"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Sha Wujing come from?",
              "answer": "Staff"
            },
            {
              "question": "Which ranking type does Caduceus come from?",
              "answer": "Staff"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "difficulty": "Hard",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "What is the **2nd** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Firestorm Shrine"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **3rd** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Green Mall"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **4th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Sun-Drenched Meadow"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **5th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Wet Wet Wonderland"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **6th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Domain of Dreams"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **7th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Juju jungle"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **8th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Deadly Desert"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **9th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Lovers Glacier"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **10th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Autumn Leaf Crags"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **11th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Ravaged Battlefield"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **12th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Electric Town Akihabara 2.0"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **13th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Sky Palace Madora"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **14th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Mashup Mechalopolis"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **15th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Hyperdrive Stadium"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **16th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Candy Cottage"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **17th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Enarius Undersea Temple"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **18th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Alice Bowling Alley"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **19th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Alaster Palace Library"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **20th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Colosseum"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **21st** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Butterfly Botanical Garden"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **22nd** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Burning Purple Festival"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **23rd** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Fang Forest"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **24th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Battlefield Paradise"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **25th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Sadistic Party"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **26th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Crashdub Club"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **27th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Thunder Storm Mountain"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **28th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Tempest of Burning Purgation"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **29th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Snow Nostalgia"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **30th** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Moonlight Old City"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the **31st** Normal quest area called?",
              "answer": "Cherry Blossom Castle"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much REC does a healing fruit give?",
              "answer": "7"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much REC does a Mega healing fruit give?",
              "answer": "21"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much REC does a Giga healing fruit give?",
              "answer": "70"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much REC does a Tera healing fruit give?",
              "answer": "140"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do hatters cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "2000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do caterpillars cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "1500"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do Little Humpties cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "4000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do Master Keys cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "3000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do Giga fruits cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "1400"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much do Ducksworths cost in the Ghost store?",
              "answer": "700"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many floors does Solo Challenge Tower have?",
              "answer": "25"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Merksha?",
              "answer": "Painter of Love"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Rodan?",
              "answer": "Silent Pteranodon Attack"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Chiemi?",
              "answer": "Love at first fright"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Red Hare?",
              "answer": "Red Hares on Horseback"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Mr.Whale?",
              "answer": "Call of the Great Whale"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Mjölnir?",
              "answer": "Selection by Lightning Round"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Haydn Ogre?",
              "answer": "Kitty meet Murderous mouse"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Terabell?",
              "answer": "Death to the Beast"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Mikado?",
              "answer": "Unhand my bride"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Witch Octopus?",
              "answer": "Ready to Become Human"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Unicorn?",
              "answer": "Solitary Unicorn"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Chika?",
              "answer": "Crimes and Concoctions"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Shizuka Gozen?",
              "answer": "Red-Hot Dancer"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Gael?",
              "answer": "The Hammer That Falls"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Hook?",
              "answer": "Croc Hunter on a Warpath"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Yuki?",
              "answer": "'Til Hypothermia Do Us Part"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Serket?",
              "answer": "Poison God's Plea"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Ja Ridalsa?",
              "answer": "Paranoia Art"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Cyclops?",
              "answer": "Heartless Executioner"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Kanetsugu Naoe?",
              "answer": "Heaven, Earth and Man"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Nelson?",
              "answer": "One-Armed Admiral"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Yuya?",
              "answer": "Animal Assassin"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Ranmaru?",
              "answer": "The Lord's Right-hand man"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Versailles?",
              "answer": "Firelight Beauty"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Humbaba?",
              "answer": "Beasts of the Dark"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Pazuzu?",
              "answer": "Morphing Wind"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Archelon?",
              "answer": "The Listless Bookworm"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Leedsichthys?",
              "answer": "Glutton for Punishment"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Kaede?",
              "answer": "Thumbs in the air"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Sen no Rikyu?",
              "answer": "The Journey Begins"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Byggvir & Beyla?",
              "answer": "Fairy Blockade"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Land Dragon?",
              "answer": "Red Dragon Sanctions"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Nasu no Yoichi?",
              "answer": "Zero-One Game"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Motojiro Kajii?",
              "answer": "Lemon-Colored Shock"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Lindworm?",
              "answer": "Steel Predator"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Reflect&MIRROR?",
              "answer": "The Beautiful but Deluded Queen"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Iria",
              "answer": "Mediator Among Friends"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Sparta?",
              "answer": "Endurance and Obedience"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Misako?",
              "answer": "Ashes to Ashes"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Ahemait?",
              "answer": "Soul-Slaying Shadow"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Megalodon?",
              "answer": "Terror of the Deep"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Nue?",
              "answer": "Thundercloud Assassin"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Lisa?",
              "answer": "Suffocation Cometh"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Siren?",
              "answer": "Siren Song"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Parvati?",
              "answer": "It's all for the Master"
            },
            {
              "question": "Who rules the the five Queens?",
              "answer": "Queen of Hearts"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get in total from missions for clearing all Normal quests?",
              "answer": "350"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get in total from missions for the first 10 days of playing Crash Fever?",
              "answer": "500"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get in total from missions for reaching rank 50?",
              "answer": "250"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get from the mission for logging in a total of 100 days?",
              "answer": "200"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get from the mission for logging in a total of 200 days?",
              "answer": "100"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get from the mission for logging in a total of 365 days?",
              "answer": "50"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon do you get from the mission for logging in a total of 500 days?",
              "answer": "200"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is Chunhyang also known as?",
              "answer": "Haruka"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the Haruka also known as?",
              "answer": "Chunhyang"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the maximum amount of Polygon obtainable from a 7 day Membership?",
              "answer": "150"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the maximum amount of Polygon obtainable from a 30 day Membership?",
              "answer": "1075"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the maximum amount of Polygon obtainable from a 90 day Membership?",
              "answer": "4300"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many units are there in the database?",
              "answer": "2182"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Lupine Guzzler Woolfe?",
              "answer": "The Better to eat you with"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Urashima?",
              "answer": "The Battle for Ryugujo"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Lessa & Gigan?",
              "answer": "Backstreet Brawl"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Odr?",
              "answer": "The Seeker of Truth"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Hydra?",
              "answer": "Cannoball Capers"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Fernyiges?",
              "answer": "The Radiant Dragon on High"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Gjallarhorn?",
              "answer": "Melody of the Weekend"
            },
            {
              "question": "What green unit may drop from the Link hatcher?",
              "answer": "Genbu"
            },
            {
              "question": "What blue unit may drop from the Link hatcher?",
              "answer": "Seiryu"
            },
            {
              "question": "What red unit may drop from the Link hatcher?",
              "answer": "Suzaku"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is the name of the quest where you obtain Anastasia?",
              "answer": "Hand Over that Glass Slipper"
            },
            {
              "question": "What yellow unit may drop from the Link hatcher?",
              "answer": "Byakko"
            },
            {
              "question": "A unit that has a skill cooldown of 23 before enhance will have what skill cooldown after enhance?",
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many levels are required to fully upgrade an Ultimate quest unit's skill?",
              "answer": "16"
            },
            {
              "question": "A unit that has a skill cooldown of 22 before enhance will have what skill cooldown after enhance?",
              "answer": "7"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many levels are required to fully upgrade a Wizard quest unit's skill?",
              "answer": "5"
            },
            {
              "question": "How many levels are required to fully upgrade a Hatcher unit's skill?",
              "answer": "7"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP does an awakened frog give to a unit of the same color?",
              "answer": "150000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much EXP does an awakened frog give to a unit of a different color?",
              "answer": "100000"
            },
            {
              "question": "How much Polygon in total can be obtained from the New Friend Bonus?",
               "answer": "1400"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]},
      {
        "topic": "Units",
        "questions": [
          {
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "questions": [
            ]
          },
          {
            "difficulty": "Medium",
            "questions": [
            ]
          },
          {
            "difficulty": "Hard"
          },
          {
            "questions": [
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "topic": "Quests",
        "questions": [
          {
            "difficulty": "Easy",
            "questions": [

            ]},
          {
            "difficulty": "Medium",
            "questions": [

            ]},
          {
            "difficulty": "Hard",
            "questions": [

          ]}
        ]
      }]
    }
